[
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Newton"],
    "questionText": "What is the unit of Force?",
    "options": ["Newton", "Watt", "Joule", "Pascal"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Rotational effect of force"],
    "questionText": "Torque is a measure of?",
    "options": [
      "Amount of force",
      "Rotational effect of force",
      "Distance of force",
      "Angle of force"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Increase in force"],
    "questionText": "What is Mechanical Advantage?",
    "options": [
      "Reduction in work",
      "Increase in force",
      "Increase in distance",
      "Increase in speed of doing work"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Exhaust ,Power ,Compression ,Intake"],
    "questionText": "What are the four strokes in the engine?",
    "options": [
      "Exhaust ,Power ,Compression ,Intake",
      "Power ,Compression ,Exhaust ,Intake",
      "Exhaust ,Intake ,Power ,Compression",
      "Power ,Compression ,Intake ,Exhaust"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Wheel wrench"],
    "questionText": "Which tool is used to open the wheels of a car?",
    "options": ["Wrench", "Screwdriver", "Spark plug wrench", "Wheel wrench"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Dipstick"],
    "questionText": "Which instrument is used to check engine oil level?",
    "options": ["Dipstick", "Torque wrench", "Feeler gauge", "Hydrometer"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Battery charger"],
    "questionText": "Which device is used to charge the vehicle battery?",
    "options": ["Alternator", "Battery charger", "Starter motor", "Regulator"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["To rotate the crankshaft"],
    "questionText": "What is the function of the piston in the engine?",
    "options": [
      "To burn fuel",
      "To compress air",
      "To rotate the crankshaft",
      "To open and close valves"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["To mix fuel and air"],
    "questionText": "What is the function of carburetor?",
    "options": [
      "To filter fuel",
      "To mix fuel and air",
      "To cool the engine",
      "To lubricate the engine"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Movement of pistons and valves"],
    "questionText": "What does the timing belt control?",
    "options": [
      "Movement of pistons and valves",
      "Fuel injection timing",
      "Engine temperature",
      "Engine speed"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["To decrease or stop the speed of the vehicle"],
    "questionText": "What is the main function of brake system (System Brake)?",
    "options": [
      "To increase the speed of the vehicle",
      "To decrease or stop the speed of the vehicle",
      "To change the direction of the vehicle",
      "To cool the engine of the vehicle"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["To absorb shocks and provide a comfortable ride"],
    "questionText": "What is the main function of the vehicle suspension system (System Suspension)?",
    "options": [
      "To provide fuel to the vehicle",
      "To rotate the wheels of the vehicle",
      "To absorb shocks and provide a comfortable ride",
      "To change the direction of the vehicle"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["To transfer power from the engine to the wheels"],
    "questionText": "What is the basic function of transmission system?",
    "options": [
      "To transfer power from the engine to the wheels",
      "To start the vehicle",
      "To provide electricity to the vehicle",
      "To measure the speed of the vehicle"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["To cool the engine"],
    "questionText": "What is the main function of cooling system (System Cooling).",
    "options": [
      "To lubricate the engine",
      "To cool the engine",
      "To provide fuel to the engine",
      "To control engine speed"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["According to the manufacturer's instructions"],
    "questionText": "When should engine oil be changed?",
    "options": [
      "Every 1000 kilometers",
      "Every 5000 kilometers",
      "Every 10000 kilometers",
      "According to the manufacturer's instructions"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["According to the manufacturer's instructions"],
    "questionText": "What should be the air pressure in car tires?",
    "options": [
      "PSI 10",
      "PSI 20",
      "PSI 30",
      "According to the manufacturer's instructions"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["All of the above"],
    "questionText": "When should brake pads be replaced?",
    "options": [
      "When the brakes make noise",
      "When the brakes take longer to stop the vehicle",
      "When the brake pads become thin",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["All of the above"],
    "questionText": "If the engine does not start, what could be the possible cause?",
    "options": [
      "Dead battery",
      "Faulty starter motor",
      "Lack of fuel",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["All of the above"],
    "questionText": "If smoke is coming out of the car, what could be the possible cause?",
    "options": [
      "Burning engine oil",
      "Burning transmission fluid",
      "Coolant leak",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["All of the above"],
    "questionText": "If car tires are wearing out quickly, what could be the possible cause?",
    "options": [
      "Low tire pressure",
      "Wheel alignment",
      "Poor quality tires",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Refrigerant"],
    "questionText": "Which gas is used in car air conditioning systems?",
    "options": ["Carbon dioxide", "Nitrogen", "Refrigerant", "Oxygen"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["To cool the coolant"],
    "questionText": "What is the function of a car radiator?",
    "options": [
      "To cool engine oil",
      "To cool transmission fluid",
      "To cool coolant",
      "To cool the battery"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Sulfuric acid"],
    "questionText": "Which acid is used in a car battery?",
    "options": [
      "Hydrochloric acid",
      "Sulfuric acid",
      "Nitric acid",
      "Carbonic acid"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Exhaust"],
    "questionText": "What causes a car engine to produce smoke after burning fuel?",
    "options": ["Piston", "Spark plug", "Cylinder", "Exhaust"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Brake sign"],
    "questionText": "What Warning sign appears when the car's brakes fail?",
    "options": ["Engine sign", "Battery sign", "Brake sign", "Oil sign"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Spark plug"],
    "questionText": "What ignites the fuel in a caar engine?",
    "options": ["Piston", "Spark plug", "Cylinder", "Exhaust"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": [
      "Transferring engine power to the wheels and controlling the car's speed"
    ],
    "questionText": "What is the function of a gearbox in a car?",
    "options": [
      "Starting the car",
      "Increasing the car's speed",
      "Changing the car's direction",
      "Trasferring engine power to the wheels and controlling the car's speed"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Compression"],
    "questionText": "What is used to ignie fuel in a diesel engine?",
    "options": ["Spark plug", "Compression", "Carburetor", "Injector"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["To reduce engine noise"],
    "questionText": "What is the function of a car silencer?",
    "options": [
      "To reduce engine noise",
      "To cool the engine",
      "To increase the car's speed",
      "To change the car's direction"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["All of the above"],
    "questionText": "What information is written on the sidewall of a car tire?",
    "options": [
      "Tire size and load index",
      "Tire manufacturing date",
      "Tire pressure",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Carburetor or fuel injector"],
    "questionText": "What causes the mixture of fuel and air in a car engine?",
    "options": [
      "Silencer",
      "Carburetor or fuel injector",
      "Battery",
      "Radiator"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["All of the above"],
    "questionText": "Which part of the car needs to be replaced regularly?",
    "options": ["Tires", "Air filter", "Brake pads", "All of the above"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Light brown or transparent"],
    "questionText": "What color should the engine oil of a car be?",
    "options": ["Black", "Red", "Light brown or transparent", "White"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Lead"],
    "questionText": "Which metal coating is applied to the terminals of a car battery?",
    "options": ["Gold", "Silver", "Copper", "Lead"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["All of the above"],
    "questionText": "Which gauge is used to check a certain aspect of the car engine?",
    "options": [
      "Fuel gauge",
      "Temperature gauge",
      "Pressure gauge",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Light yellow"],
    "questionText": "What color should the brake fluid of a car be?",
    "options": ["Black", "Red", "Light yellow", "Blue"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Spark plug"],
    "questionText": "What cause the explosion of fuel in a car engine?",
    "options": ["Piston", "Spark plug", "Cylinder", "Exhaust"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["To absorb shocks from the road"],
    "questionText": "What is the function of a shock absorber in a car?",
    "options": [
      "To increase the car's speed",
      "To absorb shocks from the road",
      "To provide fuel to the car",
      "To change the direction of the car"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Nitrogen"],
    "questionText": "Which gas is usually filled inside car tires?",
    "options": ["Oxygen", "Carbon dioxide", "Nitrogen", "Helium"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Gear oil"],
    "questionText": "What type of oil is used in a cat's transmission?",
    "options": [
      "Engine oil",
      "Brake fluid",
      "Gear oil",
      "Power steering fluid"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Transmission"],
    "questionText": "Which part of the car transfers the engine's motion to the wheels?",
    "options": ["Brake", "Suspension", "Transmission", "Steering"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Oil pump"],
    "questionText": "What helps pump oil in a car engines?",
    "options": ["Water pump", "Oil pump", "Fuel pump", "Air pump"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Carburetor or fuel injector"],
    "questionText": "What ensures the correct ratio of fuel and air in a car engine?",
    "options": [
      "Silencer",
      "Carburetor or fuel injector",
      "Battery",
      "Radiator"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Friction material"],
    "questionText": "What are brake pads made of?",
    "options": ["Rubber", "Steel", "Friction material", "Plastic"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Lead and antimony"],
    "questionText": "Which metals are used in a car battery?",
    "options": [
      "Lead and antimony",
      "Copper and aluminum",
      "Iron and nickel",
      "Silver and gold"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Refrigerant"],
    "questionText": "Which gas is used in car air conditioning systems?",
    "options": ["Carbon dioxide", "Nitrogen", "Refrigerant", "Oxygen"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Brake booster"],
    "questionText": "What helps increase the force applied to the brake pedal in a car?",
    "options": [
      "Brake lines",
      "Brake drums",
      "Brake booster",
      "Master cylinder"
    ],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Cylinder"],
    "questionText": "In which part of the car engine does the mixture of fuel and air burn to create energy?",
    "options": ["Cylinder", "Crankshaft", "Piston", "Valves"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Spark plug"],
    "questionText": "What in a  car engine creates the spark that ignites the fuel?",
    "options": ["Battery", "Starter motor", "Alternator", "Spark plug"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  },
  {
    "lang": "ENGLISH",
    "codeSnippet": null,
    "correctAnswer": ["Compression"],
    "questionText": "What is used to iginite fuel in a diesel engine?",
    "options": ["Spark plug", "Compression", "Carburetor", "Injector"],
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "optionsType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "language": "TEXT"
  }
]
